Guide to the Stanley Milgram Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1954-1993; Series III
  - Speeches
    - Gentle Aggressor, University of Iowa (1965), 1963-1965 (Box 71, Folder 300)
    - Legitimation of Evil, APA (1965 Sep 4) (Box 71, Folder 301)
    - Obedience, Harvard (1966 Jan 13), 1966 January 13 (Box 71, Folder 302)
    - Obedience to Authority (1966 Apr 25), 1966 April 25 (Box 71, Folder 303)
    - University of Michigan (1967 Oct), 1967 October (Box 71, Folder 304)
    - Violence as the Outlet, Northwestern University (1968 Jan), 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 305)
    - A Conceptual Analysis of Institutionally Generated Aggression, San Diego (1968 Mar 3) (Box 71, Folder 306)
    - Conceptual Analysis of Obedience (1968 Oct 24)
    - Conceptual Analysis of Obedience, University of Missouri (1968 Oct 31) (Box 71, Folder 307)
    - The Psychological City, City University (1968 Nov 20), 1968 November 20 (Box 71, Folder 308)
    - University of Delaware (1969) (Box 71, Folder 309)
    - City Living, Vassar College (1969), 1969 June 6 (Box 71, Folder 310)
    - Sarah Lawrence College (1969 Jan 16), 1969 January 26 (Box 71, Folder 311)
    - University of Pennsylvania (1969 Feb 19), 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 312)
    - T.V. Violence (1969 Apr 23) (Box 71, Folder 313)
    - Ten Variations on a Theme by Asch, York University (1969 Jun) (Box 71, Folder 314)
    - Washington (1969 Sep) (Box 71, Folder 315)
    - The Individual, Conscience and Authority: Experimental Studies, Wellesley College (1969 Nov 17) (Box 71, Folder 316)
    - An Experimental Analysis of Obedience to Authority, Harvard (1969 Nov 19), 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 317)
    - The Experience of Living in Cities, Adelphi University (1969 Dec 10) (Box 71, Folder 318)
    - Nonverbal Communication and Deafness, New York University (1970 Jan 23), 1970 January 23 (Box 71, Folder 319)
    - The Psychological Analysis of Destructive Obedience, Wright Institute (1970 Feb) (Box 71, Folder 320)
    - The Psychological Analysis of Destructive Obedience, Wright Institute (1970 Feb) (Box 71, Folder 321)
    - University of Chicago (1970 Feb) (Box 71, Folder 322)
    - MIT (1970 Feb 18) (Box 71, Folder 323)
    - The Experience of Living in Cities, Columbia University (1970 Mar 6), 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 324)
    - State University of Albany (1970 Mar 11), 1970 March (Box 71, Folder 325)
    - State University of New York (1970 Apr 10) (Box 71, Folder 326)
    - New York University (1970 Apr 23), 1970 April (Box 71, Folder 327)
    - University of Utah (1970 May), 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 328)
    - Obedience, Manhattanville College (1970 May 11) (Box 71, Folder 329)
    - Obedience, University of Massachusetts (1970 Oct) (Box 72, Folder 330)
    - The Experience of Living in Cities, Case Western Reserve University (1970 Nov) (Box 72, Folder 331)
    - Alternatives to Aggression, New England Psychology Association (1970 Nov), 1970 November (Box 72, Folder 332)
    - The Dilemma of Obedience, NBC (1971 Mar 28) (Box 72, Folder 333)
    - University of Laval, Quebec (1971 Apr), 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 334)
    - Public Broadcasting Audience Research, Ford Foundation (1971 Apr) (Box 72, Folder 335)
    - University of Rhode Island (1971 May 6) (Box 72, Folder 336)
    - Experience of Living in Cities, University of Cincinnati (1971 May 14), 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 337)
    - Experience of Living in Cities, University of Utah (1971 May 17), 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 338)
    - Brigham Young University (1971 May 18), 1971 May 19 (Box 72, Folder 339)
    - Obedience, University of Montana (1971 May 19) (Box 72, Folder 340)
    - Yale University (1971 Nov 17) (Box 72, Folder 341)
    - Harvard University (1971 May 5), 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 342)
    - T.V. Study (1971 Dec 9) (Box 72, Folder 343)
    - Television and Anti-Social Behavior, Yeshiva University (1972 Feb 17), 1972 February 4 (Box 72, Folder 344)
    - Television and Anti-Social Behavior, New School for Social Research (1972 Feb 24), 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 345)
    - Florida State and University of Florida (1972 Mar), 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 346)
    - Subway Psychology, City University of New York (1972 Apr 25), 1972 April (Box 72, Folder 347)
    - Television and Antisocial Behavior, New York Academy of Sciences (1972 May), 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 348)
    - Obedience and Institutional Aggression, John Jay College (1972 May) (Box 72, Folder 349)
    - Twentieth International Conference of Psychology - Tokyo (1972 Aug), 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 350)
    - University of Jerusalem (1972 Dec) (Box 72, Folder 351)
    - London School of Economics (1973 Mar) (Box 72, Folder 352)
    - Psychological Maps of European Cities, University of Hamburg (1973 May 15) (Box 72, Folder 353)
    - Paris Maps (1973 Sep 19), 1973 September 19 (Box 72, Folder 354)
    - Violence and Television, Harvard (1973 Nov 30), 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 355)
    - A Psychological Analysis of Urban Experience, Ohio Wesleyan University (1974 Feb 13), 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 356)
    - Urban Life, University of Dayton (1974 Mar 14) (Box 72, Folder 357)
    - The Ethical Edge, Riverdale-Yonkers Society for Ethical Culture (1974 Mar 30) (Box 72, Folder 358)
    - Intellectuals and the Popular Culture: Gains and Losses of Celebrity Status, University of Massachusetts (1974 May 9-11) (Box 72, Folder 359)
    - The City and the Self, Hofstra University (1974 May 14) (Box 72, Folder 360)
    - The Eichman Next Door, Lakeland Community College (1974 Nov) (Box 72, Folder 361)
    - Problems in the Study of Authority, The New School (1974 Dec 8), 1974 December 8 (Box 72, Folder 362)
    - Interview, University of British Columbia (1974 Dec 20) (Box 72, Folder 363)
    - New York/Paris (ca. 1974-1975), 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 364)
    - Violence and Aggression, Clemson University (1975 Feb 20), 1973-1975 (Box 72, Folder 365)
    - The Psychology of Obedience in Nazi Germany, Princeton University (1975 Apr 7) (Box 73, Folder 366)
    - City and Self - Web of City Life: audio tape (1975 Apr 14), 1975 April 14 (Box 73, Folder 367)
    - National College of Education (1976 Jan 30) (Box 73, Folder 368)
    - Aggression, Casper College (1976 Mar), 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 369)
    - Ethics, University of Minnesota (1976 Apr 9), 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 370)
    - Obedience, Georgetown University (1976 Apr 10), 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 371)
    - Psychological Maps of Paris, 21st International Congress of Psychology - Paris (1976 Jul 20) (Box 73, Folder 372)
    - Obedience, Miami University (1976 Oct 22) (Box 73, Folder 373)
    - The City and the Self, Brooklyn College (1976 Nov 6) (Box 73, Folder 374)
    - University of California, Berkeley (1977 Jan), 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 375)
    - Hastings: includes audio tape (1977 Feb 1), 1977 February 1 (Box 73, Folder 376)
    - Controller or Controlled: The Individual in Relation to his Environment, Texas A & M University (1977 Feb 18), 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 377)
    - Obedience, John Jay College (1977 Apr 21) (Box 73, Folder 378)
    - Obedience, Association of the Bar of the City of New York (1977 May 2) (Box 73, Folder 379)
    - Terrorism, Evian, France (1977 Jun) (Box 73, Folder 380)
    - Use of Film in Psychology, APA Convention (1977 Aug 27) (Box 73, Folder 381)
    - Obedience to Authority, Kansas State University (1977 Oct) (Box 73, Folder 382)
    - Obedience to Authority, Harlem Valley Psychiatric Center (1977 Oct 29), 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 383)
    - The Problem of 42nd Street, CUNY (1977 Nov 1), 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 384)
    - The Individual and Authority, New York University (1977 Nov 21) (Box 73, Folder 385)
    - Psychology and Photography, Rutgers (1977 Dec 2) (Box 73, Folder 386)
    - Obedience to Authority, University of Villanova (1977 Dec 8) (Box 73, Folder 387)
    - Polaroid talk, Cambridge, MA: includes audio tape (1977) (Box 74, Folder 388)
    - Ithaca College (1978 Feb 9), 1978 February (Box 74, Folder 389)
    - Ethics talk, The Hastings Center (1978 Mar), 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 390)
    - Interpersonal Communication, Montclair State College (1978 Apr 13) (Box 74, Folder 391)
    - Obedience, University of Tennessee (1978 Apr 20) (Box 74, Folder 392)
    - The Problem of Obedience in a Just Society, Jerusalem (1978 Jun) (Box 74, Folder 393)
    - Social Representations, Paris (1979 Jan 9), 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 394)
    - Celebrations, Yale (1979 Aug) (Box 74, Folder 395)
    - Photography, American Academy of Arts and Sciences (1979 Feb 10), 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 396)
    - Obedience, The American University (1979 Mar 1), 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 397)
    - Royal Military College, Canada (1979 Mar 19) (Box 74, Folder 398)
    - The City and the Self, Denison University (1979 Apr 10), 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 399)
    - Obedience, St. John's College, Minnesota (1979 May 1), 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 400)
    - City Life, York College (1979 May 4), 1979 March (Box 74, Folder 401)
    - Role of Deception in Research, PRHR conference - Boston (1979 Oct 26), 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 402)
    - Photography in Psychological Focus, New England Psychological Ass. (1979 Oct 27) (Box 74, Folder 403)
    - Oberlin (1980 Jan), 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 404)
    - Authority in the Realization of Human Potential, Chicago (1980 Mar), 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 405)
    - The Psychology of City Life, Loyola University of Chicago (1980 Apr 18), 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 406)
    - Obedience, Iona University (1980 Apr 25), 1980 February 21 (Box 74, Folder 407)
    - Social Psychology in the 80's, Fordham University (1980 May 3) (Box 74, Folder 408)
    - Union College (1980 May 16) (Box 74, Folder 409)
    - The Teaching of Ethics in Social Psychology, Vassar College (1980 Jun 11) (Box 74, Folder 410)
    - Obedience From the Perspective of 1980, Oklahoma (1980 Nov) (Box 74, Folder 411)
    - Obedience, College of Mount St. Vincent (1981 Feb 17), 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 412)
    - Obedience Interview, Claremont Men's College (1981 Apr 21) (Box 74, Folder 413)
    - Berkeley (1981 Jun) (Box 74, Folder 414)
    - Obedience, William Paterson College (1981 Oct 30) (Box 74, Folder 415)
    - Cities and Social Behavior, North Carolina State University (1981 Nov 5) (Box 74, Folder 416)
    - Obedience, Youngstown State University (1981 Nov 19), 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 417)
    - Authority: a Sociobiological Analysis, Political Science Conference - CUNY (1982 Dec 10) (Box 75, Folder 418)
    - Psychology of Destructive Obedience, Kent State University (1983 Apr 14), 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 419)
    - Obedience, University of Chicago (1983 Apr 27) (Box 75, Folder 420)
    - Obedience and Conflict, West Chester State College (1983 May 6) (Box 75, Folder 421)
    - 1984, University of Delaware (1983 Oct 10) (Box 75, Folder 422)
    - Obedience From the Perspective of "1984," CUNY (1983 Dec 15), 1967-1983 (Box 75, Folder 423)
    - Catherine Genovese and the Urban Experience, Fordham University (1984 Mar 10) (Box 75, Folder 424)
    - Obedience From the Perspective of "1984," La Salle College (1984 Apr 7) (Box 75, Folder 425)
    - The Psychology of Urban Life, Baylor University (1984 Apr 25), 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 426)
    - Obedience From the Perspective of "1984," University of Tennessee at Martin (1984 Apr 26), 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 427)
    - Cyranoids, APA Talk: includes audio tape (1984), 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 428)
    - City Life, Urban Experience (no date), Circa 1981-1984 (Box 75, Folder 429)
    - Lost Letter (no date) (Box 75, Folder 430)
    - Obedience (no date) (Box 75, Folder 431)
    - Studies in Obedience: audio tape (no date) (Box 75, Folder 432)
    - Photography (no date) (Box 75, Folder 433)
    - Photography lecture, media class (no date)
      - General, Undated (Box 75, Folder 434)
      - Audiorecordings
        - Tape 1, 1 (Box 75.1)
          - Use copy, 1 (Box 75.1U)
        - Tape 2, 1 (Box 75.2)
          - Use copy, 1 (Box 75.2U)
  - Films, Completed
    - Obedience
      Reproductions of Outtakes are are labeled "Obedience Experiment (Condition 25)."
      - Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 75, Folder 435)
      - Financial records, 1962, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 436)
      - Instructions for film maker, audio tape, Undated; 1 (Box 76.1)
        Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
        - Preservation master, 1
        - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 76.1D)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 76.U1)
      - Narration, audio tape, Undated; 1 (Box 76.2)
      - Narration, script, Undated (Box 76, Folder 439)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 76, Folder 440)
      - Outtakes: original picture (restricted), 1963 (Box 77)
      - Outtakes: original picture (restricted), 1963; 4 (Box 78.1–78.4)
      - Outtakes: original sound (restricted), 1963 (Box 79)
      - Outtakes: synchronization of picture and sound (restricted), 3 (Box 80–82)
        - Grand masters, 1993; 3 (Box 83.1–83.3)
        - Duplicating masters, 1993; 3 (Box 84.1–84.3)
      - Outtakes: Outtakes: synchronization of picture and sound (restricted), edited version, 1993; 1 (Box 85.1)
        - Duplicating master, 8
        - Use copy 1, 1 (Box 85.1U1)
        - Use copy 2, 1 (Box 85.1U2)
      - Publicity, 1969, undated (Box 85, Folder 448)
    - The City and the Self
      - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 449)
      - Drafts, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 450)
      - Drafts, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 451)
      - Music track, audio tape, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 452)
      - Narration and outline, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 453)
      - Notes, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 454)
      - Publicity, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 455)
      - Reviews, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 456)
      - Scripts, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 457)
    - Invitation to Social Psychology
      - Award, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 458)
      - Correspondence, 1974, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 459)
      - Milgram's notes, Undated (Box 86, Folder 460)
      - Narration drafts and outlines, Undated (Box 86, Folder 461)
      - Notes to the instructor, Undated (Box 86, Folder 462)
      - Showing, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 463)
      - Review
      - Videotape Bobbo doll sequences, Undated (Box 86, Folder 464)
        See: f 471
    - Conformity and Independence
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 465)
      - Shooting script, Undated (Box 86, Folder 466)
      - Milgram's notes, Undated (Box 86, Folder 467)
      - Narration (script & 2 audio tapes), Undated (Box 86, Folder 468)
      - Notes to instructor, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 469)
      - Outlines and drafts, Undated (Box 86, Folder 470)
      - Review, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 471)
    - Nonverbal Communication
      - Correspondence, 1973, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 472)
      - Film expenses
        See: box 87, folder 479
      - Outlines and drafts, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 473)
      - Milgram's notes, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 474)
      - Notes to instructor, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 475)
      - Pictures, Undated (Box 86, Folder 476)
      - Review, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 477)
    - Human Aggression
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 478)
      - Film expenses, Undated (Box 87, Folder 479)
      - Milgram's notes, Undated (Box 87, Folder 480)
      - Notes to instructor and study guide, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 481)
      - Outlines and drafts of script, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 482)
      - Production matters, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 483)
      - Schedule, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 484)
      - Stills, Undated (Box 87, Folder 485)
  - Films, incomplete
    - New York-Paris
      - Background material, Undated (Box 87, Folder 486)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 87, Folder 487)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1980, undated (Box 87, Folder 488)
      - Film proposals and drafts, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 489)
      - Grant proposals, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 490)
      - Interviews: audio tapes, Undated (Box 88, Folder 491)
      - Interviews: audio tapes, Undated (Box 88, Folder 492)
      - Interviews: audio tapes, Undated (Box 88, Folder 493)
      - Interviews and background sounds: audio tapes, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 494)
      - Interviews by Joyce Wackenhut, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 495)
      - New York film segments, 1978-1979 (Box 89)
      - Notebook, Undated (Box 90, Folder 496)
      - Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 497)
      - Paris audio tape and film notebook, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 498)
      - Paris audio tape segments, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 499)
      - Paris audio tape segments, Undated (Box 90, Folder 500)
      - Paris film segments, Undated (Box 91)
      - Paris film segments, Undated (Box 92)
      - Paris film segments, 1979, undated (Box 93)
    - The Life Cycle in and Urban Setting, Circa 1974 (Box 94, Folder 501)
    - Inculcating Urban Skills Through Film, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 502)
    - Ethics in Human Research
      - Correspondence and notes, Circa 1976 (Box 94, Folder 503)
      - Grant proposal, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 504)
      - Outlines, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 505)
      - Proposal for EVIST, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 506)
      - Proposal to EVIST, 1977-1980 (Box 94, Folder 507)
    - Candid Social Psychology, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 508)
    - Ethnomethodology, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 509)
    - Another Time, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 510)
- Teaching Files, 1960-1984; Series IV
  The materials in this series are organized according to the course for which they were used, in chronological order. Courses are listed under the university at which they were given; courses at Yale University appear first followed by those at Harvard University, and City University of New York. Course numbers are noted in parentheses after the course title.
  - Yale University
    - Psychology of the Small Group (56a), 1960 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Psychology (20b), 1962 Fall (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Psychology (20b), 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Psychology (20b), 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Current Literature in Social Psychology (149), 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Research Techniques in Social Psychology and Personality (101b), 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Research Techniques in Social Psychology and Personality (101b): "Lost Letter" study, 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Research Techniques in Social Psychology and Personality (101b): "Lost Letter" study, student papers, 1963 Spring (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Harvard University
    - Social Relations (98), 1964 Fall (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Social Relations (98): "Johnson-Goldwater Lost Letter" study, 1964 Fall (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Social Relations (98): "Johnson-Goldwater Lost Letter" study, student papers, 1964 Fall (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Social Relations (291), 1964 Fall (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Social Relations (207b), 1965 Spring (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Social Relations (291), 1965 Fall (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Social Relations (291): "Charitable Conformity" study, data, 1965 Fall (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Social Relations (291): student papers, 1965 Fall (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Social Relations (207b): student papers, 1966 Spring (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Social Relations (281), 1966 Spring (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Social Relations (98), 1966 Fall (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Social Relations (98): "Three Cities" study, 1966 Fall (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Social Relations (98): "Three Cities" study, student papers, 1966 Fall (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Social Relations (291), 1966 Fall (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Social Relations (291): "Diffusion Feedback" study, 1966 Fall (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Social Relations (291): student papers and assignments, 1966 Fall (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Social Relations (301), 1966 Fall (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Social Relations (302), 1966 Fall (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Social Relations (207b), 1967 Spring (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Social Relations (207b): student papers, 1967 Spring (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - Student tutorial, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous course materials: includes audio tapes, 1965, undated (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - City University of New York
    - Social Psychology Current in Field Settings (U801.4), 1967 Fall (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.4): "Crowd" study, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.4): "Crowd" study, student papers, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): "History" lecture notes, 1968-1984 (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - International Social Psychology (U801.14), 1968 Spring (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - International Social Psychology (U801.14): student papers, 1968 Spring (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1968 Fall (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): "Images of Psychology Experiment" study, 1968 Fall (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1968 Fall (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1969 Spring (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1969 Fall (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1969 Fall (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1969 Fall (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): Ethics survey, 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): student papers and assignments, 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers and assignments, unused studies, 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802): student papers, 1970 Spring (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1970 Fall (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1970 Fall (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - Experimental social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 53)
      - Expenses, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 54)
      - "Familiar Stranger" study (at train station), 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 55)
        See also: box 145, folder 19
      - "Familiar Stranger" study: photographs (at train station), 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 56)
      - "Familiar Stranger" (at CUNY) study, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 57)
      - "Familiar Stranger" (at CUNY) study: data, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 58)
      - "Familiar Stranger" (CUNY) study: photographs, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 59)
      - Student papers: "Familiar Stranger", 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 60)
      - Student papers: "Familiar Stranger", 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 61)
      - Student papers: "Familiar Stranger", 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 62)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 63)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802): student papers, 1971 Spring (Box 97, Folder 64)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 65)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers and assignments, 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 66)
    - Independent Psychology Research (U802), 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 67)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.04), 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 68)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.04): student papers and assignments, 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 69)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.04): subway study data, 1971 Fall (Box 97, Folder 70)